Stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make a stand!
The paint within brings
out a map of your own.
To the left and the right
all we saw stormy nights.
All the rough winds and
waves coming day after day?
And the values we had were about to
collapse Oh just where do we go next?
And as we look down to the compass in
hand Is it showing us the right direction?
All we know is nobody
here knows it for certain.
So close your eyes and breathe in deeply.
And listen to your soul.
You'll see a path in front of you.
And you'll know just where you need to go.
So stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make us stand.
Don't let the darkness
win, just break through.
I'll do it my own way,
that's what's best for me.
And you do it your way,
that's how it's got to be.
We're moving forward, now I'm ready.
But at times it's okay
to get help on the way.
For the future ahead, burning bright.
For what's ahead you see?
Is beyond your wildest dreams.
So stand up tall, reach out your hand,
cut through the wind and make A stand,
don't let the darkness
win, just break through.
We'll do it our way,
the best that we know.
With tears and doubts and tone,
we'll go where we all want to go.
The page within brings colors of our own.
See, I'm a lover, but I'm also a
fighter, man or woman, I like it rough.
Hoiron Knuckles!
It's hard to find a good punching bag.
But you're just the perfect size!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
A smack his face in!
Huh? Oh my!
Running away?
Marco!
For the record, these webs
aren't just here to block you.
They're all so extremely flammable.
Hurry up, sir!
What was it you said?
This will be over before you know it.
You're nothing but talk.
You thought you were some kind of
hero coming to Blackleg's rescue.
You're every bit as quick as he was.
And now, you'll make a fool
of yourself, just like he did!
Come on, little flower!
Try to blow me the sea of flame!
We both know your wilt, so do it!
Wither and die!
That demon child shouldn't
be allowed to live.
Do this world a favor and die!
You little heathen.
It's just like I told you.
You're a liability.
A burden to your crew mates.
You would think you're something special.
Powerful people from all
over the world have their
eyes on you because you
can read the bone glyphs.
But that's it.
Sure.
Just a tool to them.
As long as they can use you.
Who needs a personality.
Who Who needs legs?
Having a tramp like you in your place
is just so satisfying.
Now look, you ran all over the place
and now the entire hall is on fire.
You made a real mess.
Call your friend here,
a skeleton with a sword.
He'll clean up your trash like last time.
If he cares enough to bother.
These are very foolish things
you're saying, Black Maria.
And I suspect you'll be
regretting your actions shortly.
I'd run if I were you.
Robin? Hello?
Are you listening?
I said get over here!
You need to learn to punch.
Let's go!
I don't like hitting people with my fist.
We're talking about a life
or death struggle here.
Just a slap won't be enough.
I see okay, then how
about using your palm?
I know palm strikes to focus on speed over
strength Throw it quick
and pull it back quick.
It's easy.
Robin meet your new secret weapon.
The dragon claw fist.
Excuse me. Who invited you?
I'm gonna teach Robin.
So you buzz off. Come on.
It doesn't matter who teaches her
Then I will no I will
you aren't even a teacher
though I'm a fishman karate
assistant instructor.
That's enough both of you leave her
be hey I'm helping robin's grappling
techniques are all she needs I'm
just worried because we won't be
able to protect her anymore after
she leaves I'm telling you she's
perfectly capable but our fishman karate
techniques would pair so well with
robin's fighting style not as well
as my techniques would if you ask
me she has her own way of fighting
you have to respect that that's what
I'm saying it's great for palm strikes
sure but it would be devastating
with the dragon claw fist or her
palm why don't you let robin speak
there's still something I want to hear
you say robin tell me you want to live
help me robin help me please
I've never thought about becoming
stronger for someone else's sake
would you stop worrying I'll handle
this why don't you stop worrying and let
me handle it all right a palm strike
sounds perfect show
me okay you don't
mind sharing your secret techniques
of course not why would I mind you're
one of us we love
you watch
like this
when you're You're in a tight spot.
You can use this palm strike.
It's a Fishman Karate secret arc.
Help me afloat.
Fishman Karate?
Well, well, what's this?
I can't eat up!
Where were you even aiming?
A pawn strike.
You've put my pawns to
good use again and again.
Find your enemy's core, then strike it!
Find the core and strike.
Dammit, the fire!
Cheap planless?
What the hell are you?
Stay back!
Let go of me!
You are wrong.
There are people in
this world who need me.
Who love me.
And rely on me.
And I'd do anything for them.
Anything.
Even turn into a demon.
Grand jacuzzi, love you!
Did you hear that, sisters?
Lady Black Maria is going in for the kill.
I'm sure that tramp is begging for mercy.
Stop!
No!
Who needs arms and legs, you said?
No, no, no, no, no!
I need my arms and legs!
I'm talking about yours, you bitch!
What was that?
Lady Black Maria?
What happened?
I can't see anything!
Stupid skeleton in a stupid ice!
Hello, Lady Black Maria?
Lady Black Maria?
What's wrong?
My lady, what happened to you?
Oh!
My team!
I'm considerate of you all to line up.
That'll make this much easier. Yo-ho-ho!
And now...
Rockdown's orchestra!
There you are, Robin.
Welcome back.
Thank you, Park, for waiting for me.
I made it.
But I'm afraid I'm a little tired.
Rest easy now.
I don't think you appreciate
my situation here.
That is a whole month's worth
of my food you're eating, pal.
You better return the favor once
we're done with this whole mess.
How did you have so much food
with you in the first place?
Thanks to the power of my swamp, Swamp
Fruit, I'm like a bottomless pit.
Hey, Straw Hat, what happened
to the captain up there?
Is he still alive?
Happy Eel guy!
I beg of you!
Please use your power!
There is no other way!
I'm capable of doing it! Yes!
But why would you want this?
Luffy needs me!
I have to help him!
Help him!
It's not over!
The battle must be won!
And that means we're going back up there!
My lord, how could you say such a thing?
Going back to that place is suicide.
You can't.
It's too dangerous.
I won't allow it.
And yet, you must.
If we lose, then nowhere we'll be safe.
Not just the capital, but
the land of Guano itself.
I'm aware of the danger.
I'm as frightened as anyone.
But I must go.
And to do that, I need your aid.
Lord Momonosuke, listen carefully.
My power only works one way.
If I do what you ask,
there's no turning back.
The years that you sacrificed
will never return to you.
Your mind will remain the same, but
your body will become that of an adult.
After all you've been through, a
sacrifice like that is simply too much.
I don't care!
What I need right now is to
become a full-grown dragon!
No!
I can't!
I could never do such an awful thing.
Forgive me, my lord,
but you must reconsider.
Please, I beg of you, we can
find another way. We can't.
There's no time.
Please, use your right, right jutsu.
And make me into an adult.
I'll grow up for my
country and for its future.
You must use your power on me!
The 5,400 troops of the Samurai Pirate
Alliance made a raid on Onigashima,
facing 30,000 Beast Pirates.
But that gap in numbers diminished
in time thanks to Otama's Kimidango
strategy and the valiant efforts of
Luffy's allies all over the island.
Now, even the high-ranked
Tobiropo have been defeated.
Yet, Onigashima continues
its trek to the mainland.
And soon its dark shadow will loom
over the unsuspecting flower capital.
Why would you serve that wretched beast?
You know that Orochi has
no right to the throne!
As ninja, our duty is to serve the
Shogun, not question his legitimacy.
I need you!
How annoying!
You call Odoshield, Rex,
but you serve a failure!
A mere ghost!
You speak ill of war, Odin! There you are!
Karoo!
You always let your emotions
get the better of you?
A true ninja very such weaknesses!
Even your mighty techniques will fit you!
It is those very emotions that drive
us that give us joy and purpose.
Every moment we spent
with Lord Odin was a gift.
We cried together We laughed
together, and when our lord died,
we died with him.
We are but ghosts now, bound by
the thread of Lord Odin's dream.
Our duty is not some burden to bear!
It is our pride, emboldened by every
feeling we shared with Lord Odin.
A dream worth dying for!
Tonight, the darkness of Orochi
and Kaido will come to an end!
And tomorrow will bring
a bright future to Wano?
Then a new arrow will be poured
with Lord Momonosuke Ashokan!
Another one down.
Damn, Marcus.
How many stand-ins do you have?
Precious few, I'm afraid.
You've butchered them.
Such a waste of life.
I'll kill you! Ahhhh!
Ahhhh! Come on!
Ahhhh!
There are only a few left but the
question is whose lives do they contain?
What happened it's like something just
stabbed me what the hell happened!
No, don't tell me it's him.
Ah, you figured it out.
I was having fun. For a moment,
I thought you might cut your own captain
to shreds without realizing it was him.
But that's all right.
Now that you know you can't win,
I'll enjoy watching you fall
deeper and deeper into despair.
Your vow to defeat me has
been rendered meaningless.
You can only strike me down by
killing your beloved partner.
You bastard! Master! Master!
It tickles my imagination,
thinking of all the uncertainty and
suffering you're hiding behind that mask.
I'm ready.
Entertain me.
Kill me if you dare.
You are sick!
Out of my way, Trafalgar!
The price of betrayal
is very steep indeed.
That's right.
Not even your new Straw Hat pals can
save you from what you've got coming.
It's execution time, and
your rats are getting bad.
He's a friend alive!
Somebody help us!
Where did Markham go?
He reached his physical limit.
We'll have to do this on our own.
Sangoro, are you all right?
Oh, sure, it just tickles.
I can't fight both of them at once.
Do you want us to find Zoro
Judo so he can finish him off?
Pull it together, boss head.
Does it normally take this long to work?
I've never seen it used with
such extensive injuries.
Hey, Chopper! Miyagi!
If the drug's not
working, take Mummy Judo?
And get the hell out of here!
Don't worry, we injected him,
so it should take effect soon.
Keep fighting, Zoro!
Hang on, we have to find
some way to stop those two.
At this rate, they're going to wipe
out everyone on the entire floor!
Find Roro, Noah, Zoro!
Kill him while you still can!
They gave him some strange treatment!
Don't allow him any time to recover.
You shouldn't turn your back on me!
You got this, Scar!
Real cute, you punk!
I'm not gonna let you
bastards cut down anyone else!
Dimwitted Dance.
You kicked up so much
dust I can barely see!
I'm gonna lickety-stickety
you, Vinsmoke Sanji.
This is personal.
If you had Merry Pudding
like Mama planned,
we wouldn't be here right now
teaming up with a bunch of idiots!
That's him, master?
I see.
Go to hell, worthless jammer scum!
Let's take this outside, shall we?
I'm here to avenge Pedro!
There is no escape.
I found Dorry!
Everyone follow me!
Let's butcher him!
The Beast Pilate!
Zoro Juno fought for Wado, so
we'll fight to protect him. Yeah!
Those samurai are all wounded!
We can finish them off at
the same time as Rhino!
We'd better follow them!
We still don't know what's
going to happen to Zoro!
We got it!
Oh, King Pluton!
You're really making me work
today, aren't you, Mosshead?
Better get out of our way, Blackleg!
It's over!
It's pure your plan!
A dying thistle!
I heard a story about this long ago.
On top of the Great Red Wall,
It dwelled a race of people
who've been burst into flames.
King the wildfire.
I get it now.
I didn't expect to see you alive.
Marco!
The white deer pirates off the roof!
Give up already!
Fine.
I surrender.
I'm satisfied now.
I've hogged the spotlight for long enough.
And now it's time for the
real star to take the stage.
Roronoa!
Diably!
Three-sword style.
Purgatory!
You need to get me!
All right, straw hands, where to show us?
That dog!
It's a miracle!
Yeah, but I'm worried about later.
Hey, Curly Browns.
You know what happens if
we win this battle, right?
We'll cross the threshold
into the final stretch
and get a glimpse of Luffy
becoming King of the Pirates.